what's going on ladies and gentlemen
welcome back to another one as you can
see we're on the water we're going to be
doing a little bit of a product review
today on a product that I'm super
excited about we recently did the old
model of this reel and we're going to be
doing a new one it's actually the PC fun
carbon X2 now we got the 2000 size reel
and this thing is awesome it's ultra
light this thing is awesome okay I'm
super excited to talk about it we're
going to break it down on what I think
of this thing and hopefully we can catch
some fish while we're doing it we're
going to be throwing a wacky rig today
we've been trying to catch some fish
it's been kind of tough I'm hoping we
can hook into them today the water's
been super high we've just had like 2 ft
of rain in the last like couple weeks so
kind of crazy but we're going to jump
into it guys we're going to do a review
on this thing stay tuned and let's see
what we think all right so as we jump
into things I want to talk about this
reel tell you what I think about it and
kind of just go from there and when I
say this reel is super smooth I mean it
is incredibly smooth okay featuring an
all carbon body rotor and slide this
thing is one of the lightest reels that
you can buy on the market and honestly
it puts in work when you reel it in it's
so smooth I mean smoother than any reel
I've honestly used in a long time and
they just feel really good
ooh we might have been getting bit Oh no
just a weed that's all
right I'm super excited to test out the
new reel because these things are
awesome okay I have used the carbon X
I've never used the carbon X2 before
this is my very first time and I wanted
to be able to give you guys kind of my
first thoughts on this reel and so far I
tell you what this thing seems awesome
okay it is a 621 gear ratio and that's
perfect that's pretty standard for
spinning as far as spinning reels go and
you can definitely tell that it's one of
the smoothest reels out there um
especially with its price range is
$74.99 if you go on their website now I
think typically it's more than that but
you can get a pretty good deal on this
thing right now as it sits so 75 bucks
for a super super good reel you kind of
can't go wrong the casting power on this
reel is pretty incredible I put a 20 lb
braided line on here with a mono backer
at the beginning and this thing can cast
a long ways I think I actually just
where did I land that wow that thing
went a long ways it casts with ease and
one of my favorite Parts about it kind
of like the carbon X if you guys can
hear
it the drag sounds super nice on this
thing the drag is super smooth a lot of
times you know with your cheaper
spinning reels the drag can be you know
kind of iffy and you know this guy not
iffy at all the drag Is Awesome on this
thing and I love it the spool capacity
it says if you put a 15 lb braided line
on that it'll fit 150 yard or if you put
8 lb of mono on it'll at 120 Y and
honestly that's plenty if you're going
through 150 yards a
line you probably need to get you
probably need to up your uh reel and set
up anyway because you got to have a
pretty big fish to spool spool you on 15
or 20 lb line okay I did coming in at
7.2 Oz for a 2000 Siz Rod or reel excuse
me is a pretty great weight for this
kind of reel I mean honestly it feels so
light in your hand 7.2 Oz feels like
nothing you can buy a lot of other reels
that honestly just feel kind of heavy
and drag you down and you don't want
that you know when you're trying to
finesse these fish if you're fishing for
a real light bite that kind of thing you
don't want your real dragging you down
in that sense some of the differences
between the carbon X and carbon X2 you
have a much lighter reel here they did
adjust this knob at the top your drag
knob is bigger which is kind of nice
it's easier to adjust if you're reeling
a fish I need to do it on the Fly
um well we're going to give this spot a
try that last spot was not the move
there was no fish
there this is a pretty good spot we're
going to get ourselves out of the wind a
little bit I do notice more vegetation
than normal but we're going to give it a
shot one thing thing that is pretty
notable about this reel is it has 22 lbs
of drag which is honestly pretty sweet
for reeling in big fish if you throw 20
or 30 lb braid on this thing you can
practically Crank That braid all or that
drag all the way down and reel the fish
over the top of the water if you want if
you're fishing you know deep cover that
kind of thing and I think that is a huge
bonus a lot of reels don't have that
much drag so that's kind of something to
note and like I said
before and with this reel there's a 11
St stainless steel sealed bearings and
with that I do believe that this reel is
going to stand the test of time being
that those bearings are sealed you
should be able to use this reel for a
long long time without it ever going bad
I didn't add any grease or oil or
anything to this reel and it's as smooth
as can be I'm super super happy about
this reel and I'm excited to use it for
a long long long time oh oh weed man
where are all our fish come on the hand
is foam on this rail and honestly I
really like it it seems to be grippy
just grippy enough but not too slippery
to like slip your hands off of it and
that kind of thing but it is just a foam
grip there and I really like it it keeps
the real lightweight a lot of reels have
a big heavy rubber reel on it you just
don't really need that the foam grip
works perfect and it fits super good in
your hand I love the way that this comes
down here the body is great like I said
it's all carbon I think if you guys are
looking for a reliable affordable high
quality fishing reel I think you should
definitely check out the PC fund carbon
X2 I like the 2000 size rods reels
excuse me I uh haven't actually used a
PC fun reel in any other size so I can't
speak so I can't speak for those but I
can tell you that the 2000 series reels
really have something going for them
they're so lightweight the the bearings
are good the gear ratio is good at a 621
gear ratio you got to love it that's
everything you need in a spinning reel
all around just an incredibly vers vers
atile reel I think you could use this
for Crappie fishing walleye F fishing
bass fishing um just about
anything but if you check that out guys
I mean that's a pretty far cast for a
weightless senko you really can't go
wrong on this next cast I'm going to I'm
going to give it everything I have and
show you guys what this thing can
do all right here we go I'm going to
give this a cast and I'm going to cast
it as far as I can and show you guys
just how far it casts okay here we
[Music]
go I mean that thing's way out there in
a wind and everything and that's right
where I kind of I wanted to put it so
can't go wrong I mean I was just going
for power on that one but it doesn't
throw too much line off the spool and it
casts super far so if you're looking to
make long casts this can do
it all in all though guys if you're
looking for a super reliable
awesome lightweight spinning reel I
would definitely consider checking out
the PC fun carbon X2 I do like the 2000
series reels but you could get it for
any size you wanted they do make a 500
series reel for ice fishing as well and
you can get it in three different colors
I believe there's like a purple and a
teal color which is kind of cool I just
got the black cuz I think the black
looks super nice but if you guys want to
check it out I will link it in the
description and make sure you use my
code
jj15 to save yourself an additional 15%
off at check out and all in all though
guys I would definitely recommend
checking this reel out and I hope you
guys enjoyed the video and we'll see you
in the next one peace